http://www.myron.com/privacy-policy

QUICK SERVICE NUMBER
To activate special promotions, enter your Quick Service Number from any mailing & catalog you've received from Myron.Not on our mailing list? Register online today!
Please enter a Quick Service Number
We did not find your QSN. Please try again or give us a call.
Submit
Close
Sign up for Exclusive Offers
Sign up Today & SAVE $20 OFF $200!Join our email list to be the first to know about new promotional products, exclusive offers, and more!
Please enter a valid email address
Submit
Close
Thank you!You are subscribed to Myron’s promotional emails, now it's time to save!Please check your email for your $20 OFF coupon code.
Your email is already subscribed.
An error occurred signing up to our newsletter.Please try again at a later time.
Login
Customer Service
1-877-803-3358
QUICK SERVICE NUMBER
To activate special promotions, enter your Quick Service Number from any mailing & catalog you've received from Myron.Not on our mailing list? Register online today!
Please enter a Quick Service Number
We did not find your QSN. Please try again or give us a call.
Submit
Close
Did you mean to enter a Quick Service Number?
Please enter a Quick Service Number
We did not find your QSN. Please try again or give us a call.
Forgot your password?
Enter Your Quick Service Number (QSN) Below For Your Special Offer!
At Myron, our purpose is to help our customers grow their businesses and promote themselves
using personalized products. We are equally committed to respecting your privacy.
This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) explains how Myron collects and uses personal information, and the choices you
can
make. This Policy applies to your use of Myron.com and other services that link to this Policy. This Policy also
addresses information we collect from you when you inquire about our products, place an order, when you contact
one
of our customer service or sales representatives, or when you respond to a survey or other promotion that we
administer.
We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy in its entirety before using our services. By creating an online
account, using our services, or making a purchase, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to this Privacy
Policy.
What personal information do we collect? How do we use that information?
How do we share your information with third parties?
What options do you have to limit our collection and use of your personal information?
How do we keep your information secure?
How do we make updates to this policy?
How can you contact us with questions about your privacy or this Policy?
Supplemental Notice to California Residents
What personal information do we collect? How do we use that information?
We collect various types of personal information when you register with our websites,
mobile
sites or systems (our “Sites and Apps”); purchase any products or services from us; contact one of our customer
service or sales representatives; register for customer rewards programs; or complete a survey or enter a
contest or
promotion that we sponsor. This information may be collected directly from you (for example, when you complete
our
forms or enter your information on our websites to make a purchase) or indirectly through your device or browser
when you visit our sites.
We use your information to fulfill product orders, to customize and improve the advertising and content you see,
to
offer suggestions for personalized products based on your content, to deliver marketing communications and
promotional materials that you may be interested in, to contact you and provide customer service, to protect the
security or integrity of our databases or websites, to detect and prevent fraud or illegal activity, to take
precautions against liability, to detect and remediate violations of our Terms of Use or other misuse of our
sites,
to develop and improve our products and services, and for internal operational purposes.
The following chart describes what categories of personal information we may collect, how we collect that
information from you, the business purposes for which we generally use such information, and which types of
trusted
third-party service providers we may share that information with:
Information Type
Source
Purpose
Third-Party Sharing
Direct Identifiers (Customer Name, Postal Address, Phone Number- E-mail
Address)
User-generated content (including logos, graphics, & photos)
Payment information (credit card information, only last four digits are
stored,
checks)
Provided directly by customer
Processing payments on your orders
Detecting security incidents and protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or
illegal activity
Payment and chargeback processors
Fraud prevention and site security
Purchase information (purchase date, purchase totals, product types)
(IP Address, Cookies, Website Browsing and Interaction Activity, Other Device
or
Browser Identifiers)
Collected indirectly from customer’s browser or device
Enhancing your user experience
Analytics to improve our products and services
Advertising and marketing our products to you
Detecting security incidents and protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or
Detecting security incidents and protecting against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or
illegal
activity
None
Inferences about customer preferences and characteristics
Inferred from information provided by customer and information collected
In addition to any personal information that you might provide when you do things like buy
our
products or create an account, we may also have access to other information about you if you interact with us
via
social media.
Social Media
If you log into your account through a social media site, we will also have access to
certain
information from that site, such as your name, account information and profile photo, in accordance with the
site’s
account verification procedures. Also, if you interact with content on our social media profiles (for example,
if
you “like” or share a post from one of our brand’s Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram accounts), those social media
sites may share information about you with us, including your public profile, e-mail address and friend list. If
you
choose to “like” or share content, information about you may be publicly displayed on the social network,
depending
on your privacy settings. You should review the privacy policy of that social media site and check your privacy
settings through that site. If you post information on a social media or another third-party service that
references
our brands or our products and services (e.g., via a Twitter hashtag), we may publish your post on our social
media
accounts or websites.
Information You Provide About Others
The content you choose to upload to our web site or send to us may include personal
information
of others (for example, an employee list). Before you upload and/or share personal information of others through
our
service, please ensure that you have the consent of such persons to do so.
Cookies
We and our service providers collect information about how you use our services – for
example what web or mobile pages you have viewed – to analyze trends, generate analytics, provide a better user
experience, improve our products and services, detect and prevent fraud or security incidents and gather broad
demographic information for aggregate use. Our sites use pixel tags, web beacons, and similar tracking
technologies (collectively referred to as “Cookies”) that are created when you use our online services and are
stored on your computer or mobile device.
Cookies help us offer convenient features like storing the contents of your shopping cart until you are ready to
check out, remembering your login and account settings, recognizing your browser when you visit, customizing
your current and future visits, and providing you with information about products that interest you. Cookies
help us personalize your experience and save time during checkout. We also use the information we collect to
compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our site to monitor site traffic, develop marketing
programs, and improve our website design and content.
We use the information collected by our third-party service providers using Cookies to analyze and track data,
improve our services, determine the popularity of certain content, and better understand our users’ online
activity. Our service providers may also show you advertisements for our products and services on other
websites, and may combine this information with other information those service providers have gathered about
your visits to those other websites so that the advertisements you receive are more likely to be of interest to
you.
Other Sources
We may also obtain data that is publicly available or from third party sources, such as
address verification services, to improve the accuracy of and add to what we know about our customers and
prospective customers. We may combine this publicly available information with your personal information for
the purposes described in this policy.
Employment
In addition to information collected from our customers, we and our service
providers also collect certain information from candidates who apply for a job with Myron to contact you
about your application and evaluate your qualifications for the position, including your name, phone
number, e-mail address, postal address, education information, and employment information.
How do we share your information with third parties?
We may share the personal information we collect with affiliated third parties for
our marketing or order processing purposes.
We may “rent” customer contact information to affiliated or approved brokers, just
as we may “rent” similar information from such brokers. We also may share personal information in the
following situations.
Service Providers
We sometimes use third-party service providers to act on our behalf, for example to
help us fulfill your product orders, process payments, enhance and personalize your shopping experience
with us, or to deliver our advertisements. Our service providers may receive your name and contact
information, payment information and other content you upload to our sites or send to us, information
about purchases you’ve made, cookies and other device identifiers, IP address, and website browsing and
interaction activity. These service providers are only allowed to use your information in connection
with the specific service they provide on our behalf.
Law Enforcement, Mergers, and Other Situations
We may be required to share your personal information in other, limited
circumstances. For example, we may be required to share certain information to respond to a subpoena or
similar judicial process, to comply with state, federal or local laws, to protect the security or
integrity of our databases or website, to take precautions against liability, in the event of a
corporate reorganization or, to the extent required by law, to provide information to law enforcement
agencies. Additionally, your information may be transferred to another organization if, for example, we
transfer the ownership or operation of the Sites and Apps because we have merged with or have been
acquired by another organization, or if we liquidate our assets. In those cases, the new company’s use
of your information will still be subject to this Policy and the privacy preferences you have expressed
to us.
What options do you have to limit our collection and use of your personal
information?
You have choices about how your information is collected and used. You can notify
us of your preferences when you create an account with us, and if you would like to review, correct or
delete your account information on our sites and apps, you can do so by logging in to your account or by
contacting us directly. There may be times when we are unable to fulfill your request – for example, if
providing access to your personal information would reveal confidential commercial or proprietary
information or personal information about someone else (and we cannot separate your data), if we are
prohibited by law from disclosing the information, or if we have a legal obligation to retain certain
data, or if removal of such data would compromise the integrity of our data. We may require additional
personal information from you for the purposes of verifying your identity and rights.
If you are a resident of California, please see the section below entitled “Supplemental Notice to
California Residents” to learn more about your rights.
Opting out of Marketing Communications
If you no longer want to receive marketing communications from us, you can
unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages you receive, by changing your marketing
preferences through your Account Settings, or by contacting us through the Contact Us page on our web
site. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the products and services we
provide, such as service announcements and administrative messages (for example, communications related
to a pending order, an unresolved customer service issue, or a policy update). We do not offer you the
ability to opt-out of receiving those communications.
Cookie Options
If you don’t want our sites and apps to collect information using Cookies, you can
change your web browser settings to reject Cookies from the site or to alert you before a cookie is
placed on your computer. Each browser is different, so you should check your browser’s “Help” menu to
learn how to change your cookie preferences. Please note that cookie-based opt-outs only apply to the
specific computer and browser on which the opt-out cookie is applied. If you accept a cookie, you can
delete it at any time through your web browser. If you choose not to accept Cookies, though, you will
not be able to enjoy all the features available to our registered users.
The Network Advertising Alliance (“NAI”) and the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) offer opt-out
tools to help you manage your choices for participating companies that use Cookies for Interest-Based
Advertising and cross-app advertising. For more information about these tools please visit: NAI Opt-Out
Page and DAA Opt-Out Page.
You can also opt out
of Google cookies by installing Google
Analytics’
opt-out browser add-on https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout, and/or the
Google Advertising Cookie
out-out browser add-on.
“Do Not Track” is a preference you can set in your web browser to let the sites you visit know that you
do not want them collecting information about you. Our sites may or may not respond to all “Do Not
Track” settings of all browsers and browser versions.
How do we keep your information secure?
Although no website, application, database or system is completely secure or
“hacker proof,” we have safeguards in place to protect against unauthorized access and disclosures
of the personal information we control, including technical, physical and administrative safeguards
and security measures. Despite these measures, however, we cannot guarantee that our information
security safeguards will never be compromised.
Our sites and apps may be linked on other websites or may contain links to other websites. Our
Privacy Policy only applies to our sites and apps, and we are not responsible for the privacy
practices, security standards, or content of other sites. You should check the privacy policies of
those sites before providing your personal information to them. See our Terms of Use for additional
information.
How do we make updates to this policy?
As we implement new technology and introduce new services or otherwise change
our privacy practices, or in response to changes in applicable laws or regulations, we may modify
this Policy and provide notice to you by posting updates on this page. Please check back
periodically to view any updates. Changes to our Policy will become effective when posted. If we
change this Privacy Policy in a material way, we will endeavor to promptly notify our customers.
Your continued use of our websites, mobile applications and/or other services following such notice
acknowledges your acceptance of such updated terms.
How can you contact us with questions about your privacy or this Policy?
For further information regarding this website privacy statement or related
Myron policies and procedures, please contact us via email at: service@myron.com.
Supplemental Notice to California Residents
Effective Date: January 1, 2020
If you are a California resident, California law may apply to how we collect and use your personal
information, and what rights you have in some circumstances. The following terms supplement our
Privacy Policy and explain the rights of California residents.
For information about what categories of personal information we may collect from our customers, the
sources of that information, the purposes for collecting and using that information, and what types
of third-party service providers we may share that information with, please see our section titled
What personal information do we collect? How do we use that information?
California residents have the following rights:
The right to request information about personal information that we have collected about
that customer in the 12 months preceding the customer’s request (including the categories of
information collected, the source of that information, the business purpose of that
collection, the categories of third parties with whom that information is shared, and the
specific pieces of personal information collected about that particular customer);
The right to receive requested information in a readily-usable format if provided
electronically;
The right to request that we delete any personal information about the consumer that we have
collected (although we may be entitled to retain some information for certain purposes);
The right to opt-out of “sales” of personal information to third parties, if applicable; and
The right to freely exercise your rights without being denied goods or services.
We cannot respond to your request to access or delete information unless we are able to both
verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information
relates to you and/or your household. If you have an account on any of our sites and apps, we
will verify your identity by having you log in to your account. If you do not have an account on
our sites and apps, we will attempt to verify your request by asking you to provide identifying
information that we will match to information in our files. We will only use information you
provide in your request for the purpose of verifying your identity or authority to make the
request. You can also designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. Your agent
will need to provide a Power of Attorney authorizing the agent to act on your behalf, or will
need to complete the same verification procedures that would be required for a request submitted
by you directly, and provide information that allows us to verify your authorization.
We may deny deletion requests in whole or in part as permitted or required by applicable law. We
do not charge a different price or rate or provide a different level or quality of goods or
services based on your exercising your CCPA rights. We do not sell personal information.
To exercise your rights under California law, please contact us as follows:
Call our dedicated CCPA line at (800) 851-4690. Leave a detailed message if prompted to do
so.
Or request online https://www.myron.com/ccpa-form
Or send an email to ccpa@myron.com
Please specify in your request which account your request relates to and the specific
information or content that you would like removed. Please note that your request does not
ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, due to legal and
other reasons listed prior in the Privacy Policy.
Back To Top
QSN: K12008996
|
MK: 08996
.
Thank you!You are subscribed to Myron’s promotional emails, now it's time to save!Please check your email for your $20 OFF coupon code.
Your email is already subscribed.
An error occurred signing up to our newsletter.Please try again at a later time.
JOIN & SAVE $20 OFF $200!
SUBSCRIBE
Please enter a valid email address
STAY CONNECTED:
© Myron Corp. | 205 Maywood Avenue, Maywood, NJ 07607 |
1-877-803-3358
